I came from the sky!
Please don't say nyan nyan nyan
Good morning
Good morning, sir.
Where are you?
This is the "Sequence" section.
This is the main section.
We've been doing a lot of "Oni" type projects.
So today we're going to give you a taste of the maid café.
I feel like I've already lied about that.
Well then, let's proceed into the ladies!
Let's go! Yes!
Wait a minute.
Today, we are a maid café where you shouldn't grin!
No! I can't! I can't! I can't! I can't!
Can't you just grin and bear it?
Let's lower the price.
From the moment you walk through the front door of this store.
I've been counting the number of times you've grinned.
What? What's that?
I was just about to grin.
Is that a bad idea?
I'll grin when I open it, in case you're wondering.
I see.
Of course, the person with the highest count
I can handle the punishment.
Oh, my God!
There it is! It's already a mite!
Now, let's start from the place where you went through!
Yay! Yeah! Yes!
Three.
Please, please, please.
Ladies, you're home.
Anyan!
Thank you!
Aaahhh!
Boo-Boo is a first-time customer, so we have a lamp and a debut set.
You can choose one of our maids, and she'll give you a special original link.
What do you want to do?
Everyone is having a great time!
I'm purple... come in purple!
What should I do?
What?
Wait a minute.
Can I ask you a favor?
Can I ask you for a favor?
May I? Thank you very much.
Then you can welcome me.
Thank you very much.
Please.
And one more dish, as much as you like.
This one!
Definitely this one!
Seino!
Omaeesu!
Here you go!
Ta-da!
Thank you!
Oh! That's great!
That's amazing!
It's so cute!
Ta-da!
Yeah!
She's so cute!
It's so cute!
This drink tastes good enough as it is, but I have a spell to make it taste even better.
I've been waiting for it!
I would like to start with a lecture.
Please have someone serve you sushi, put a big heart on it, and tell them to make it taste even better.
Be delicious!
Now, I'm going to get it from Mr. Jesse, and from the right side, moe-moe-nyan!
Meow!
Se-no!
Be delicious! Meow meow meow!
Yummy!
Delicious!
Ah! Oh, my gosh! It's purple!
It's pink!
Oh! It's dyed!
Yeah!
Cheers!
Bon appétit!
Yum! Oh, Moe!
Yum!
Blueberry!
Yummy!
It didn't taste so tired.
It tasted good, but it was delicious.
Surprise! It tastes good!
Sweet!
Now, since the maid who nominated the drinks had not yet introduced herself, please start by introducing yourself, Non-chan.
My name is Non-chan, the maid with the sand and sandy soil of Watanabe, the newspotter. I look forward to working with you.
My name is Non-chan, a maid with sand and dirt.
I am Naitome-chan, born and raised in the world of magic. Please call me Mea-chan.
Please call me Mea-chan.
Yes, I'm from the sky. My name is Kotori. Please take care of me.
Cute.
I wonder what some of you called me too.What did some call this one too?
Certainly.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm from the northeastern countryside. Please call me Karenkyun.
Karenkyun!
I'm Karenkyun!
Please call me Bineko from Miyagi Prefecture! Please!
Beautiful cat!
I've come from the sky! Please call me Nyan Nyan Yuna Nyan!
Ready! Nyan nyan yuna nyan!
He might be dead.
Here it is!
The first one is ready!
Thank you!
That's great!
This one's in, too.
What would you like me to write?
You can make a request or something.
But if you're so kind, please do a portrait!
A portrait! I'm sure!
That's great!
Cute!
So cute!
Here we go!
Next one's in!
Next!
That's great!
Linee's portrait.
Is it like her?
It's great!
Then can I write "I love you, Karen" and ask her to say it?
Is it like that?
I love you, Karen!
Boobarshi, that's so cool!
I can't help but smile, it's so awesome!
I'll leave it to you.
It's heart-squeeze time!
I got it!
Thank you very much.
It's done!
It smells so good.
Oh, my God.
It's too good to eat!
Okay.
Yummy!
Meow meow meow!
ssshhhh
From
please
Wayooooooooooooooooooo!
Landing!
Bon appétit!
Oh, yummy!
Yes, please!
Mmm...
Mmm.
Is it good?
It's all about love.
Oh, my God, it's great!
Yes, it's really delicious!
Oh, my God, it's so good!
Oh, my God.
Mmm!
Aww... ~~~~
Uh-oh.
Mmmmmm
Mooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Yum, yum!
Okay, now that we're having fun.
I'd like to hear a little bit about your current count.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I'm just having fun.
Oh, no!
Tachibana-san...
One million points!
Wow, wow, wow!
A million points.
Kitami...
Sixteen fifty-five.
What?
And...
121.
Isn't that too close?
Oh, man.
I was about to laugh.
I just open my mouth as wide as I can.
Oh, no.
It's not set in stone.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I was just getting excited.
I'm sorry.
I want to play a game.
Oh, wow.
Games? Games?
Russian octopus today.
I want to play a game.
This lady is masaosu.
I want to play a game!
Engrave, gooey, using. engra engra engra engra engra
Gok. Hey, lok. When...
I've decided squats I've decided
I've decided I'm going to do it.
By the way, you two are curlers.
That's easy to say
Oh, hey, sorry.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
I'm free.
You're kidding?
I thought you guys were so funny.
Oh, pretty.
It's going great!
So this is the next one after that?
Wait, topic!
Yes!
I'll just take one more bite of this.
Let's just take one more bite.
Ready? Ready?
Ah!
Now, that's it! That's it!
That's it!
Did you see that hand?
All of them.
Or blotches.
That's right.
The lady who made fun of me...
Okay.
Oh!
Almost all the votes are in.
Then the correct answer is
DOGDOGDOGDOGDOGDOGDOGDOGDOGDOGDOGDOGDOGDOGDOGDOGD
Then!
I was kidding!
What? Huh? Was it spicy? Wasn't it spicy?
Guess who's spicy. Huh?
Thank you very much.
It was a delicious takoyaki.
Oh, it was soooooo good.
In case you're wondering, the count will end soon, and they said there would be a penalty game just in case.
You might want to ask the maid about it.
Wait, wait, I'm really scared now.
What is the penalty?
Punishment game.
We will all be pouring a whip of love on your moe-moe pasta.
This sauce.
Oh, no.
What's more, everyone is doing it.
We will announce the count shortly.
The difference between the first and second place winner is 2.
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait. Oh no.
If we do our best, we might be able to change our ranking.
What should we do?
Have you ever had sauce, Kane-kun?
No, I haven't.
Have you ever had it at Towanska?
You haven't?
If we've come this far, we have no choice but to sleep with each other.
Yes, that's right.
I'll just wait for the count.
Yes.
The third place winner who will not be penalized is 259.
200?
Wait, you were number 100 earlier, too.
Second place is 332.
332?
First place is 339.
The Golden Seat.
It's a gold star.
What? What happens now?
We'll be punished.
No! No! No! No!
No! No!
What?
Mr. Kitami.
It's over.
It's over?
I'll start with Momose.
Excuse me.
I have a recommendation.
Oh, I'm here. I'm here.
Oh, here I am.
Subscribe to my channel!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Okay, that's it for today.
Oh, you're an angel.
Ooh!
Receive the love of the rail.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What?
So, today you received the love of the rail.
Wait a minute.
But you know what? I bet this...
I bet it tastes really good after the ritual.
Mixing and mashing performance.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Mix-mix performance.Mixed performance
Now, let's talk about the words that Meira says
The same word
Please welcome!
Now, let's have a mix-and-match performance!
Yes, yes, yes!
Ready, go!
Moe-moe-moe!
Maze-maze-maze!
Nyan nyan nyan
woof woof
Ping-pong
Mwah-mwah!
wan wan
All is right
Bon appétit!
!
pudding
ran
par
Sour!
LOL!
sour
LOL.
I'm like obsessed.
Yes, that's what I'm talking about.
This is the end of the filming.
Please subscribe to our channel.
If you liked this video, please give it a high rating.
If you liked this video, please rate it highly and subscribe!
If you liked the video, please subscribe to our channel.
Thank you very much!
So today, I'd like to thank NyanPontan for having me here.
Thank you very much for letting me join you today.
Thank you very much.
It was fun!
Nyanya!
Meow meow meow!
Please watch the next video too!
Bye bye!
BGM